#### **Denise Weber**

(330) 212-1204 dweber0001@gmail.com

#### **Personal Summary**

I am making a career change after working in the medical records field for many years. Due to offshoring, my team was laid off 11/1/2018, and I was given the opportunity as a displaced worker to obtain an associate degree in software development, which I eagerly pursued! I am now seeking opportunities in which I can integrate my prior work experience with the developer skills I have obtained, and look forward to contributing, learning and growing more in this field. Additional skills I bring: Independent long-term remote worker; positive, empathetic and optimistic attitude; strong multitasking, timemanagement and communication skills; diligent problem solver; passionate about helping, learning, growing and technology.

### **Work Experience**

# MModal (formerly MedQuist) - Franklin, TN July 2003 to November 2018

**Quality Improvement Specialist (Remote position)** 

10/2008 to 11/2018

Duties: Drive Service Delivery excellence for assigned clients via compliance with Quality Program standards utilizing live audits and positive feedback. Perform monthly assigned quality audits for clients (proofreading/editing/scoring). Due to offshoring, my entire team was laid off 11/2018.

Manager, Service Delivery (Remote position)

07/2007 to 10/2008

Managed 5 Supervisors and staff of MTs and QA staff. Daily Goals: Trained/Supported Supervisors to achieve workflow and quality goals, address stat issues. Hiring, training, PMP/PIP, termination. Responsibilities: Performance of Supervisors, MTs and QA staff in attaining TATs, quality, and customer service goals for the 105 hospitals/clinics in our book of business. Company restructure 10/2008: Elimination of all Manager Roles; I was retained in the Quality Improvement Specialist role.

QA Manager/Audit Supervisor (Remote position)

07/2003 to 07/2007

Managed 32 FTE QA Specialists. Developed QA plan to address quality issues/TAT and increase QA production. Promoted 06/2006: Audit Supervisor N Region as part of new national team. Duties: interview, hire, train team of 15 auditors. Lotus Notes Audit DB administrator. Developed training materials, led webinars, trained new auditors, liaison for database users. Promoted to Manager, SD.

### EDiX Corporation - Clearwater, FL

**August 2001 to July 2003** 

Medical Transcriptionist/Quality Editor (Remote position) - Transcribed medical reports for all specialties maintaining quality standard requirements for all reviews. Promoted to Quality Editor in October 2002, achieving 4-star monthly reviews for each period.

#### **Education**

Sinclair Community College - Dayton, OH

Graduated with Honors. Cumulative GPA of 3.41

Certificates: • IT Fundamentals 08/2020 • Fast Track Programming 12/2020

Responsive Web Design Developer Certification

September 2021

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/denise\_weber/responsive-web-design

#### Links

Portfolio: https://deniseweberdev.com https://github.com/dweber0001 GitHub:

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/deniseweber0001

# Skills

• ASP.NET (1 year)

• C++ (1 year)

 JAVASCRIPT (2 years) NODE.js/NPM

HEROKU

BOOTSTRAP

CSS3 (2 years)

PYTHON (<1 year)</li>

• REACT (<1 year) MongoDB

• C# (1 year)

• HTML5 (2 years)

jQuery

• FLASK/JINJA2

• SQL/NoSQL

## **Additional Skills**

- Medical terminology, transcription, proofreading, editing, reporting. (10+ years)
- Team building, coaching, leading virtual teams, training, assessing performance, managing performance issues, PMP/PIP, hiring, setting goals. (5+ years)
- MS Office products, research/analysis, small business accounting, QuickBooks. (proficient)